...but I can special-order it for you.
(Scene:)Him.
(Assistant:)Excuse me, sir, you don't work here.
(Sheldon:)Yes, well, apparently,
neither does anyone else.
- Sheldon, we have to go.
- Why?
(Penny:)We're late for Leonard's birthday party...
(Penny:)...and for another,
I told him to call security.
(Sheldon(to customer):)Good luck.
By the way, a 6-year-old
could hack your computer.
(Penny:)Keep walking.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, 1234 is not a secure password.
(Howard:)My friend
is having allergic reaction to peanuts.
- No, he's not.
- Yes, he is.
(Nurse:)Look, sir, we are very busy here
and I just don't...
(Nurse:)Holy crap.
Please help me.
Code four. I need a gurney.
(Nurse:)- Right away, right away.
- Thank you.
(Leonard:)Say what you will
about healthcare in this country...
(Leonard:)...but when they're afraid of lawsuits,
they sure test everything.